Guide to the Jimmy De Sana Papers 1954-1997 (bulk 1977-1990) MSS.202
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: Ephemera
  - Subseries A: Papers and clippings found throughout the Jimmy De Sana estate
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 131)
      Description: Color Photocopies
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 132)
      Description: Image Scavenger Catalog
    - Title:, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 133)
      Description: Invoice and financial papers
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 134)
      Description: JDS notes for Art Resources transfer book
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 135)
      Description: JDS notes on exposure times
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 136)
      Description: Pamphlet, "The Paintings of John Hull"
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 137)
      Description: NY Rocker Correspondence
    - Title:, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 138)
      Description: Envelope; Mrs. A. J. De Sana to Jimmy De Sana
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 139)
      Description: Photocopied portrait
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 140)
      Description: Postcards: Image Bank, Rome, Renzoni, Cortez, Patrick McMullan, John Brill, Man Ray
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 141)
      Description: Postcards: Wrongrong, JDS 1988, Seashells, Sweatshirt
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 142)
      Description: Stills from "Material Interchange"
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 143)
      Description: Submission Cover
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 144)
      Description: Thank you note
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 145)
      Description: Wedding photo, printed painting
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 146)
      Description: What's My Line? Game; John Barrymore, Gloria Swanson photos
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 147)
      Description: Holograms
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 148)
      Description: Reviews: Artforum, Artnews
  - Subseries B: Papers and clippings compiled by Jimmy De Sana
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 149)
      Zoom article
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 150)
      Anderson-Burroughs-Giorno record cover
      Art forum ad - October 1982
      SoHo Hews cover Salvador Dali/ Lene Lovich - 2 April 1980
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 151)
      Soho News cover K. Anger - 16 July 1980
      Istoe article on William Burroughs - 30 May 1984
      New Voices 2 (4 pages)
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 152)
      David Bourdon jacket
      Androgyny in Art tearsheets
      New Figuration in America papers
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 153)
      Big Car Show catalogue
      Bomb "Cowboy Hat" - Summer 1985
      SoHo News cover Laurie Anderson - 5 November 1980
      Eye cover Billy Idol - Dec/Jan 1983
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 154)
      SoHo News centerfold - 29 Novemeber 1979
      Frigidaire article - September 1981
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 155)
      American Photo- March/April 1993
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 156)
      Danceteria ad
      New York Times review - 29 January 1988
      Press clippings - 16 March 1988
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 157)
      Savvy article - July 1988
      Neo York catalogue
      Scanagraph info
      The Face clipping - November 1986
      Omni letter
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 158)
      New Times clippings - 8 January 1979
      Studio Trisorio ad
      SoHo News reproduction - 9 April 1980
      Bomb Magazine reproduction
      Body Politic K. Anger Cover - April 1982
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 159)
      Cepa Gallery Postcard
      Aperture Magazine portrait
      Art et Industrie ad
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 160)
      Talking Heads reproductions and materials
      New York Rocker Talking Heads cover
      New York Rocker Brian Eno cover
    - Title: (Box 73A, Folder 161)
      Esquire article
      New York Magazine clipping - 12 December 1988
      Actuel tearsheet
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 162)
      Vile cover
      Washington Project for the Arts: Punk art clippings
      Valentin Tatransky review
      Jimmy de Sana c.v. from catalogue
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 163)
      File Megazine clipping - Fall 1979
      Zeit Magazine clipping - October 1979
      Bomb Magazine tearsheet
      Stefanotty ad tearsheet
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 164)
      Terence Sellers / Jimmy De Sana interview
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 165)
      Oggi Domani flyer
      Omni Magazine tearsheet - March 1983
      Village Voice clippings - 26 January 1988
      File Megazine tearsheet - Spring 1976
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 166)
      Arts Magazine - May 1989
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 167)
      Postcard
      Marincola essay tearsheet
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 168)
      Bomb Magazine Cover - Winter 1988
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 169)
      Village Voice clippings - 8 May 1978
      Artifacts At The End of A Decade - 1981
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 170)
      File Megazine cover - Fall 1977
      File Megazine tearsheet
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 171)
      Image Scavengers clippings
      $bfat image
      Bomp Magazine cover - March 1979
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 172)
      American Photographer tearsheet - March 1984
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 173)
      American Photographer article - December 1983
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 174)
      Village Voice Clippings - 26 January 1988
      Exhibition Postcards (2)
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 175)
      Postcards (2)
      HK City Magazine article July 1988
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 176)
      Giant Light Bulb reproduction
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 177)
      Auto-Portraits Pompidou Center catalogue
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 178)
      Sweatshit reproduction
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 179)
      Two Holograms
      Roberta Smith NY Times Review - 29 January 1988
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 180)
      New York Contemporary Art Observer April 1988
      Vanity Fair Clippings
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 181)
      USF Galleries Pamphlet
      New Voices 2
      'You're the guy I want to share my money with" flyer
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 182)
      Art in America clippings
      Downtown cover
      Gusto Review
    - Title: (Box 73B, Folder 183)
      New York Newsday - 24 Nov 1987
      Oggi Domani postcard
      Anderson-Giorno-Burroughs album
- Series XIV: Objects
  A collection of photographic equipment and props.
  - Cameras, lenses, filters and accessories (Box 74)
  - Film loaders; agitator (Box 75)
    Description: Photographic equipment
  - Developing tubes with two lids; easel (Box 76)
  - Baby doll, rubber stamps, polaroid products (Box 77)
    Description: Assortment of objects including doll, JDS Trust stamps, unprocessed film rolls, Marilyn Minter video, film strips
- Series XV: Media
  - Subseries A: Access Copies, cuid25279
    Access Restrictions
    Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Subseries B: Originals
    Original media is generally not available for researcher use. Please see a Fales archivist for access.
    - De Sana Home Movie - Daytona - Oceanarium, 1954; ID: 202.0001 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0001)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
      General
      Original format: 16mm film
      Length: 50ft
    - De Sana Home Movie - Daytona Beach, 1954; ID: 202.0002 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0002)
      Length: 50 ft
    - De Sana Home Movie - Untitled, 1959; ID: 202.0003 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0003)
    - De Sana Home Movie - Untitled, 1959; ID: 202.0004 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0004)
    - De Sana Home Movie - Untitled, 1951; ID: 202.0005 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0005)
    - De Sana Home Movie - Untitled, 1956; ID: 202.0006 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0006)
    - De Sana Home Movie - Untitled, 1953; ID: 202.0007 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0007)
  - Subseries C: Video recordings
    - Marilyn Minter 100 FOOD PORN, undated; ID: 202.0008 (Box 79, Media ID: 202.0008)
      Original format: VHS
      Duration: 30 minutes
- Oversize Series II: Photographic prints by theme
  - Subseries E: Portrait
    20x24 silver gelatin prints
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 186)
      Delight, Duca
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 186)
      Greathouse, Timothy
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 186)
      Unknown Subject
  - Subseries F: Miscellaneous
    20x24 silver gelatin and color C prints
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 184)
      Bed (Color C Print)
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 184)
      Plastic Bags (Color C Print)
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 184)
      Shoes (Color C Print)
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 185)
      Toothpaste (Color C Print)
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 185)
      Bubblegum (Silver Gelatin Print)
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 185)
      Flour (Color C Print)
- Oversize Series XIII: Ephemera; clippings, reproductions, advertisements
  - Subseries A: Papers and clippings found throughout the Jimmy De Sana estate
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 187)
      Danceteria Ad (2)
      13-1/2x19 Moquette
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 187)
      Mask Print
      13-1/2x19
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 187)
      Wrong wrong
      15x25 Poster
  - Subseries B: Papers and clippings compiled by Jimmy De Sana
    - Title: (Box 78, Folder 187)
      James White and the Blacks record sleeve, was originally the last item in the sequence devised for this subseries by Jimmy de Sana.